Father, we call Your name.
Order every familiar spirit in our midst, out!
Wherever hidden place they are, begin to order them, Lord!
Order them, Lord!
You, familiar spirit!
You, familiar spirit, in the name of Jesus, I command you out!
I command you out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I am the spiritual husband.
I make her life miserable.
How many of you are in her?
We are three.
Who is number one and two?
Number one is...
Number two?
Number two is snake
How do you move?
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I don’t want her to have any good in her life.
Just to destroy her life, to make her miserable.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Her family – everyone is miserable.
Her grandmother sold her to me when she was five years old.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Biliki.
I am 25 years old.
I am from Nigeria but I reside in Cameroon.
Who is the lady standing beside you?
This is my mum.
She is from Nigeria too.
Tell us your story; how this evil spirit began to operate in your life right from the young age.
It started when I was little, 10 years old.
One day I was eating and I sent my junior brother to bring me some water.
Then I threw a spoon and my mum said that I wanted to kill my younger brother.
I said, "No".
She went somewhere and when she came back, she said they told her not to beat me
as I has something on me.
She asked me if it was true and I told her no.
I asked her, "Am I a king? Why are you pleading with me?"
She said it was because I had something on me, that I had a spirit of ogbanje (marine spirit) in me.
You mean that at the little age your mum actually told you that she could not beat you
because there was an evil spirit of ogbanje in you?
She said that the evil spirit was disturbing her and had blocked her way
for her not to have anything good in her life.
After she told me that, I became angry and ran away from home in 2003.
I went to a beach; there was a lady...
How old were you when you ran away from home?
I was 15 years old.
I saw a lady at a beach who told me that she wanted to take me somewhere.
We were about 10 in number.
She would always sell girls.
When she saw me, she said that I was still little, that she would not be able to sell me,
that she would keep me for herself.
She told me that she wanted to take me out of the country.
She took me to Cotonou.
When we arrived there, she told me that we were going to do the work of prostitution.
When we started, we were about 10.
She sold the rest of the girls but didn’t sell me.
She said it was still because I was a little girl.
How old were you when you went for prostitution?
I was 15 years old.
You said that the girls that were carried there - the lady in question sold them...
Yes.
But she didn't sell me because I was little.
Later, when I started, I saw a man who asked, "You little girl, come over; what are you doing here?"
I told him I was from Nigeria, that a lady had brought me there.
He asked why she had brought me there.
I told him it was for prostitution, that she said I was going to pay her some money - 200,000 naira.
The man told me to call the lady.
I called the lady for him and the man asked her, "Why do you bring this little girl to this country
to become a prostitute?"
He then gave her money and took me to a place to stay alone.
After two weeks, the man left.
When the man left, I started work, serving in a nightclub.
Men would come to me after serving them and would give me their numbers.
I would meet them and they would sleep with me.
For six years, I didn’t have any communication with my mum; no one knew where I was.
During the period you ran away from your family, nobody knew where you were?
No, nobody knew where I was for over six years.
One day, I went somewhere and the spiritualist gave me something to bathe with
so that I would be able to go home.
When I went home, I was so angry with my mum.
When I was little, I would always go to my grandmother's place.
She would give me a tablet, something like a charm
and she would ask me what I took when I went to my grandmother's place.
I would reply, "I told you I didn’t want to go there; she gave me some drugs".
As a result of those charms, I knew I was possessed with something that disturbed me
like the spirit of witchcraft because I couldn’t control myself.
The evil spirit would always push me to go out and didn't want me to stay with my family.
When you returned to Nigeria, you knew that this spirit was within you,
because you always had an urge to go out.
You didn't want to be with your family or stay with your parents whatsoever.
Yes.
I didn’t want to see any of them.
That was 2012 when I went to Niger.
I went to an herbalist as I wanted the evil spirit to be sent out of me.
I gave him money.
He bathed me and performed a ritual.
In 2012, I came back and shouted at my mum and asked her,
"When you gave birth to me, who bathed me?"
She started crying.
I ran away from home again and went to Cameroon.
Sorry. Before going ahead - you said that when you went to Niger, you went to a particular spiritualist.
Yes.
We can see some pictures here.
Is this what happened to you?
Just explain what we are seeing here.
In this picture, I gave the woman money – 200,000 naira.
She said she was going to remove the evil spirit from me.
After giving her the money, she went to buy beads and other items.
She bathed me, took me to the front of a masquerade and performed the ritual.
After everything, I noticed that nothing had changed in my life.
I later came back home and started crying with my mum.
I didn’t stay more than two or three days before getting angry.
I didn’t want to see them or be with them.
So, I went to Cameroon and started work as a…
What we are understanding from our sister is that right from the very young age - 15
she is a runaway from home.
She has not been with her parents or her family.
They have not known her whereabouts.
Even if she returned back home, it would just be for a few days, before that spirit pushed her to leave again
without any communication with her family.
She is explaining what we are seeing at the pictures here.
In the country of Niger she went to a particular spiritualist to do a ritual, which involved purchasing
a lot of different items, clothing, beads for removing an evil spirit from her life.
Despite all of these efforts the problem still continued.
She returned back to Nigeria.
Within two days of being with her family, she ran away again.
Sister, where did you go at this point?
I went to Cameroon.
I started working in Cameroon as a strip dancer.
Men would normally come to me and give me money, telling me I was a good dancer.
Miss Biliki & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
After dancing, men would give me their numbers and I would tell them I would see them after work.
One day there was a lady...
You mean in Cameroon you began working at the strip club as a stripper?
Yes.
You also continued the lifestyle of prostitution?
I would dance naked.
The men would throw money on me.
I got tired of all that I was doing.
I went to a place where I saw a woman and I explained my situation to her.
She said she didn't have anything to give me,
that what she had to give me was for me to go to T.B. Joshua at The SCOAN.
She said he would be able to deliver me.
She spoke to me on Wednesday and I decided to leave Cameroon on Thursday to arrive here on Saturday.
On my way coming, I would always go to a native doctor and pay them money after which they would
want to sleep with me and tell me that the spirit that was on me, they would have to remove it by their power
but that they would have to sleep with me.
On my way coming here, I decided to test the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua to know if he were really
a man of God and was able to locate me.
On Sunday when I came here, I was sitting down there and as he was prophesying to people,
I was looking at him thinking, "Are you really a man of God? Why can't you see me?"
As the prayer was going on, I held onto my leg tight because I didn't want to fall
but I don’t know how come I found myself on the floor.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
This is what happened last week here at The SCOAN.
We just want you to explain again, sister.
You said your reason of coming here was to test the man of God.
Yes.
Why was that?
Because I had been to many places and they would always charge me money
and later, sleep with me but nothing good would come out of it.
So, I came here to test him to know if he was really a man of God.
But I noticed that he did not even look at me, he just turned his back to me.
Then, during the mass prayer - what happened to you at that moment when the man of God began to pray?
When they started praying, I stood there and was very angry
because he didn’t even look at me or come closer to me.
He was here and I was sitting down there.
I was very angry and decided that if I left I would not come back here again.
Miss Biliki & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
I didn't know what came over me.
I saw myself at the back there.
That was how the evil spirit was exposed.
After the deliverance, when I slept, I had a dream that I saw a snake.
I always dreamt about the snake.
The snake always hit my head.
In my dream, I saw a woman and a man digging something out of the ground.
I saw a cobra.
I turned my back and when I did that, it felt as if someone had thrown the snake on me.
There was a little boy who told me that the snake was on my back and I woke up.
Sorry to cut you.
You mean to say that immediately after your deliverance the same snake that we saw manifest
during this mass prayer, was revealed to you in your dream as an evidence that you were set free?
Yes.
And you said that coming back to Nigeria - you had not seen your mum for how long?
Four years.
You mean to say that after the deliverance you have seen your mum for the first time?
Yes.
We can imagine what this evil spirit has caused in the life of our sister.
She is standing here with her mother right now.
She has not seen or communicated with her mum for so many years.
From the age of 15 she has been a runaway from the home, only to return to her mum for a few days.
For the last four years she has not been with her mum because that evil spirit always pushed her
to leave the house, run away from the family and to have such a hatred towards her parents.
As you are seeing your mum right now after your deliverance, sister; what do you have to say?
Actually I went home on Monday.
I called someone to go with me so that I would be able to take my mum's number but upon getting there,
I don't know what came over me.
I shouted our lastborn's name, "Abigail!"
That was when my mum came out, looked at me and asked, "Why?"
Then, I started crying.
That was when she told me that my father was no longer alive, that he had died two years ago.
You didn't even know that your father had died?
No.
Once again viewers all over the world; we thank God for our sister's deliverance.
As she was explaining before; it was a result of that evil spirit, that entered her right from such a young age,
to the extent that she hated her family.
She didn't even know when her own father died.
We thank God; today she is here with her mum and her eyes had been opened.
After the deliverance she realized that she has a mum and they are back together.
Sister, what can you say to the glory of God, after your deliverance?
How was your life changed?
My life has changed.
I didn’t know what came over me.
I am not the same.
I even changed my name to Jessica because I didn't want to use my real name while doing something stupid.
I had to change my name to Jessica.
Now, my real name is Biliki, no longer Jessica.
I thank God for my life and that now, I am with my mum.
Let's put our hands for Jesus Christ.
You mean to say sister; before coming to The SCOAN, you were coming from that strip club in Cameroon?
Yes.
I lied to my boss that I wasn’t feeling fine and wanted to relax for three weeks.
He said, "OK, there is no problem".
That is why I am here.
Now, after your deliverance; how do you want to go about your life?
Do you still have the mind of returning to that kind of life-style of prostitution, strip dancing?
No! I really want God to help me because I can't do it on my own.
That is why I am here.
I am tired.
I want my family to change.
I want everything to change about my life, my mum and my younger ones.
I really want people to help me because I have nobody except my mum.
If they could help me, I would be so glad.
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
Once again - we know that Jesus Christ through this deliverance has opened the door.
Our sister - you can see the tears in her eyes as a result of now regretting her past life
and having the opportunity to reconcile with her family after the deliverance.
We know that the same God who has delivered you, will definitely usher you towards the breakthrough,
that He has for you.
Finally sister, what is your word of advice to our viewers all over the world, based on your experiences in life?
My advice to viewers all over the world, girls like me – there is nothing there.
I thank God that I came out alive.
There are many girls – most of my friends whom we were together, most of them have died.
Some of them are miserable but I am still alive; I am OK.
I just want to tell people watching me to focus their minds on God.
It is only God who can change everything – no one else except God.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
We just want to hear a quick word from your mum as well.
What she has to say about your being here today to the glory of God?
Momma, you are welcome.
Just introduce yourself to us.
My name is Amuda.
I thank God that through the help of Emmanuel TV, I have been able to locate my daughter, Biliki.
Biliki had disappeared for 11 years and I had no contact with her.
When I would go to church, they would tell me that she was still alive.
On Tuesday, I saw Biliki but she did not want to come to me.
She called on Abigail who beckoned on me but I asked Abigail to confirm it was Biliki.
As I was about to get up, Abigail shouted at Biliki, "Aunty Biliki!"
This caught everyone's attention and they gathered asking Biliki why she had treated her mum that way.
I thank God for delivering her for me.
Biliki asked for her father and I told her that he had died.
Our mother is saying that for 11 years she had not known where her daughter was.
She had no idea of her whereabouts.
After receiving her deliverance on Sunday, she received news on Tuesday that someone was outside
asking for her.
Upon coming out she met with her daughter, who had come back to the house after 11 years of separation.
The mother is giving glory to God and thanking God that Jesus Christ has delivered her daughter
after so many years.
We give glory to God.
We want to encourage our sister who, is now delivered by Christ's word.
She must be ruled by His word in order to make this deliverance permanent.
We believe that best is yet to come, as you do so, in Jesus' name.
[Amen.]
After much counselling at SCOAN, Biliki and her mother are given financial support to start a new life
in Christ Jesus.
Glory be to God.
My name is Biliki.
I am 29 years old.
The woman beside me is my mum.
I want to thank God for what He has done in my life and for my deliverance.
I was here two Sundays ago.
During the mass prayer, God arrested me.
The evil spirit in me confessed and I received my deliverance.
Last week Sunday, I was here with my mum to testify of what God had done in my life.
Previously, I lived a miserable life of prostitution.
I travelled to two countries – Cotonou (Republic of Benin) and Cameroon.
I was based in Cameroon, working in a nightclub as striptease dancer.
I was meeting men.
After living this life, I didn’t gain anything from it.
Nothing good came out of the money I made.
I had not seen my parents for seven years.
So, when my father died, I did not even know.
When I came here, I got my deliverance and the man of God asked me to come with my mum.
When I came with my mum, I shared my testimony.
I thank God that I am free now.
Since then, I have been OK.
I can read my Bible and pray.
So, I thank God for my life and for what God has done in my life - for my deliverance and breakthrough.
To God be the glory.
Indeed - we thank God Almighty for the wonderful deliverance you received.
Those who were following Emmanuel TV two last weeks will really understand how mighty the deliverance
that God Almighty has done was.
We thank God also for bringing you back to your parents, whom you have lost contact with,
for so many years.
The life I was living was one of misery.
I would not wish for anyone to do the kind of things I was doing.
Most of my friends have died.
Some of them have sicknesses but I thank God that I came out alive,
safely and without injury or sickness.
I want to thank God.
To my girl friends who are watching me now, I just want to give you this advice:
It is better that you come out from it so that God can deliver you the way He delivered me.
I thank God.
My name is Amuda
What can you say about the deliverance in life of your daughter?
You are back here with your daughter to thank God for the wonderful things He has done in your life.
What can you say about what God has done in the life of your daughter?
I thank God as I have seen my daughter who has come back home.
I thank God that she has changed.
She reads the Bible and wants to start a new life now.
I thank God for T.B. Joshua.
Thank you very much.
You heard it from momma.
Momma says she is grateful to God Almighty for the deliverance in the life of her daughter.
Her daughter is a changed person now.
She can read the Bible, she can pray, she can meditate on the word of God,
unlike before, when for so many years she didn't know where her daughter was.
She was separated from the daughter because of the past life she was living.
Now she is happy to have her daughter back.
Dear sister, we also have a message from the anointed man of God to you:
now, that you are delivered and you have decided to continue a new life that you have received
in Christ Jesus, the life of holiness, and forget totally your past life -
the man of God with the support of the Emmanuel TV partners want to give you this financial support.
This is the sum of 200,000 naira and the copy of "the mirror" book.
Biliki Receives 200,000 Naira From T.B. Joshua And Emmanuel TV Partners To Start A New Life In Christ
I just want to thank the man of God for what he has done in my life, especially my deliverance.
Biliki Receives 200,000 Naira & A Copy Of The Mirror From T.B. Joshua And Emmanuel TV Partners
I just want to thank God.
Now that I am going, I am going to start a new life, sin no more and follow God's ways.
I know very soon that I will come back here with a big testimony, in the mighty name of Jesus.
Thank you very much for accepting this cash gift of 200,000 Naira given by the anointed man of God,
with the support of Emmanuel TV partners and also "the mirror" book,
which you have to read from time to time and emulate the life-style of great people of God of old,
some of which have also passed through some hard times in life and came out of it
with the help of God Almighty.
They are our "role models" today.
We believe that as you make use of this cash gift you have received, God Almighty will continue to supply
and you will come back very soon to share great testimony, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)